

Ilya Zaitsev **Frontend Engineer**

Contacts



Email godested@gmail.com



Phone

+380 63 400 6684



Website

godested.me



Location Kyiv, Ukraine

Socials



LinkedIn godested



Twitter @_godested



Instagram @ztsvi



@godested

Languages



English Upper-Intermediate



Ukrainian/Russian

Native

Professional summary

Enthusiastic frontend engineer with more than 5 years of commercial experience. Good at project development from scratch and improvement of existing solutions. Have analytical and investigative skills. Confidently understand how to build an MVP. Able to create full autonomy in frontend development. Strive to improve DX, automate code quality analysis. Familiar with unit economics. Ready to analyze business requirements, propose product and development flow improvements.

Looking for a professional workgroup to implement knowledge and gained experience, be a part of the "Big idea" project, grow and contribute, improve management and product skills to obtain a lead position in the future.

Experience



Playtech · Live

Senior Frontend Engineer

Sep 2020 - Present · 1 yr 8 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

I took a significant part in the development of 5 new games for tens of thousands of users. Was engaged in code reviews, improving DX, refactoring of existing solutions, developing new big features

TypeScript, React, Mobx, RxJS, Inversify, Webpack, Protobuf, Jest, Kibana, Jenkins.



Genesis

Senior Frontend Engineer

Mar 2019 - Sep 2020 · 1 yr 7 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

Successfully launched social app, and brand landings. Further evolution to a full-fledged product (with support, analytics, payments) was made. Had active participation in the hiring of technical specialists as an interviewer for various projects. Was a mentor for junior developers.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, Gatsby, TypeScript, WebSockets, GitLab CI/CD, Docker, Sentry, PRPL pattern.



Skywell Software

Frontend Developer

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019 · 5 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

In cooperation with a back-end developer, based on UX mockups successfully developed an application with a graphical representation of business processes in a BPMN and CMMN formats for immediate execution React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, CMMN, BPMN, Docker.



Frontend Developer

May 2018 - Nov 2018 · 7 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

Mobile-first, cross-browser, and SEO-friendly app for finding the closest money exchangers with a favorable rate was developed from scratch. Developed service for medical members with real-time calls, pptx presentations, and schedule manager.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, Mapbox, WebSockets, WebRTC, Docker.



WorkRocks

Frontend Developer

Feb 2018 - May 2018 · 4 mos Dnipro, Ukraine

Participated in the development of a real-time crypto-currencies exchanger.

React, Redux, TypeScript, WebSockets, Node.js.



Upwork

Frontend Developer

Mar 2017 - May 2018 · 1 yr 3 mos Dnipro, Ukraine

Under the supervision of a mentor, was developed a banking system and a lot of landing pages. React, Redux, WebSockets, Gulp, Node.js, Ruby.

Education



Frontend Pro

Oct 2017 - Jan 2018 Course certificate



Frontend Basic

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 Course certificate



Computer Engineering **Dnipro National University** Sep 2017

Highlights

I'm familiar with fast prototyping and release MVP for early test ideas in the real world. It took me about 3 months to analyze requirements, set up development flow, and create the first social discovery MVP (with paying customers) version of the latest released project.

I've hacked a game dedicated to the contest at OdessaJS while sitting at the OdessaJS conference 😄

